ride_name = "Millennium Falcon: Smugglers Run"

questions = [
    {
        "question": "What year did Millennium Falcon: Smugglers Run open at Disney's Hollywood Studios?",
        "answers": ["2019", "2018", "2020", "2021"],
        "correct_answer": "2019"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Disney World park is home to Millennium Falcon: Smugglers Run?",
        "answers": ["Hollywood Studios", "Magic Kingdom", "Epcot", "Animal Kingdom"],
        "correct_answer": "Hollywood Studios"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the theme of Millennium Falcon: Smugglers Run?",
        "answers": ["Star Wars", "Star Trek", "Guardians of the Galaxy", "Avatar"],
        "correct_answer": "Star Wars"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who designed Millennium Falcon: Smugglers Run?",
        "answers": ["Walt Disney Imagineering", "Tony Baxter", "John Hench", "Bob Gurr"],
        "correct_answer": "Walt Disney Imagineering"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the height requirement to ride Millennium Falcon: Smugglers Run?",
        "answers": ["38 inches", "40 inches", "44 inches", "48 inches"],
        "correct_answer": "38 inches"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the maximum speed of Millennium Falcon: Smugglers Run?",
        "answers": ["100 mph", "75 mph", "90 mph", "120 mph"],
        "correct_answer": "100 mph"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the duration of the Millennium Falcon: Smugglers Run ride?",
        "answers": ["5 minutes", "4 minutes", "6 minutes", "7 minutes"],
        "correct_answer": "5 minutes"
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of ride is Millennium Falcon: Smugglers Run?",
        "answers": ["Interactive flight simulator", "Roller coaster", "Dark ride", "Boat ride"],
        "correct_answer": "Interactive flight simulator"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the ship featured in Millennium Falcon: Smugglers Run?",
        "answers": ["Millennium Falcon", "X-Wing", "TIE Fighter", "Star Destroyer"],
        "correct_answer": "Millennium Falcon"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the character that guides you on your mission in Millennium Falcon: Smugglers Run?",
        "answers": ["Hondo Ohnaka", "Han Solo", "Chewbacca", "Lando Calrissian"],
        "correct_answer": "Hondo Ohnaka"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the planet where Millennium Falcon: Smugglers Run is set?",
        "answers": ["Batuu", "Tatooine", "Endor", "Hoth"],
        "correct_answer": "Batuu"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the spaceport in Millennium Falcon: Smugglers Run?",
        "answers": ["Black Spire Outpost", "Mos Eisley", "Cloud City", "Echo Base"],
        "correct_answer": "Black Spire Outpost"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the company that Hondo Ohnaka runs?",
        "answers": ["Ohnaka Transport Solutions", "Millennium Transport", "Galaxy Transport", "Star Transport"],
        "correct_answer": "Ohnaka Transport Solutions"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the weapon used in Millennium Falcon: Smugglers Run?",
        "answers": ["Laser Cannon", "Blaster", "Lightsaber", "Ion Cannon"],
        "correct_answer": "Laser Cannon"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the cargo you are tasked with transporting in Millennium Falcon: Smugglers Run?",
        "answers": ["Coaxium", "Spice", "Kyber Crystals", "Bacta"],
        "correct_answer": "Coaxium"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the droid that assists you in Millennium Falcon: Smugglers Run?",
        "answers": ["R5-P8", "R2-D2", "C-3PO", "BB-8"],
        "correct_answer": "R5-P8"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the hyperspace jump point in Millennium Falcon: Smugglers Run?",
        "answers": ["Corellian Run", "Kessel Run", "Hydian Way", "Perlemian Trade Route"],
        "correct_answer": "Kessel Run"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the ship's engineer in Millennium Falcon: Smugglers Run?",
        "answers": ["Chewbacca", "Han Solo", "Lando Calrissian", "Hondo Ohnaka"],
        "correct_answer": "Chewbacca"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the ship's pilot in Millennium Falcon: Smugglers Run?",
        "answers": ["Han Solo", "Chewbacca", "Lando Calrissian", "Hondo Ohnaka"],
        "correct_answer": "Han Solo"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the ship's gunner in Millennium Falcon: Smugglers Run?",
        "answers": ["Chewbacca", "Han Solo", "Lando Calrissian", "Hondo Ohnaka"],
        "correct_answer": "Chewbacca"
    }
]